

## **Personal Information**

Age: 24

Gender: Male

## Contact

Phone:

935616694

Email:

edomias888@gmail.com

Address:

Addis Ababa

## Language Skills

Amharic - Native. Amharic - Native. English - Advanced, oromic - Low, Somali - Low

# **Edomiyas Tariku**

Junior professional

#### **About**

My devotion for developing applications spans far beyond just the basics. My services are tailor-made to fit every business, to glorify every brand and to bring ideas to life, delivering only the best for clients; an application that truly portrays whilst incorporating an exceptional, unique and state of the art design that stands out from the rest. I have a Bsc degree in Software Engineering in addition to that I have 2 years worth of knowledge and experience around developing Mobile and Web-based applications for budding and established businesses by targeting their requirements .

### **Education**



Software Engineering Addis Ababa Science and Technology University GPA: 3.33

Jul 2022 **Graduation date** 

Flutter Developer

# Work experience



Dec 2022 - Present 6 month

Flutter Developer HahuCloud

I am Currently working as Flutter Developer at HahuCloud



Jun 2022 - Aug 2022 2 month

> Website developer Derash NGO

Dec 2021 - May 2022 5 month

> Mobile app developer

Ethiopian Football Federation

Feb 2021 - Sep 2021 7 month

> Website Development Wal Sounds

EPLFF is fantasy football application for the BetKing's Ethiopian premier league . I finished the project as a Lead

I have a major contribution on the development of the official

Derash Ngo website . which is designed to promote the works of the non governmental organization. Link :DerashDrdo.com

I have worked in the development of the official walsounds website. the website is used for selling all wal sounds products like Studio instruments, make ups, home appliance etc. you can buy any product via the web site

#### Certifications



Feb 2022 Certification was issued **Great Distinction Honours AASTU** 



# **Additional Skills**

Front End Developer, Graphic Design